<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://kuramu1108.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://kuramu1108.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-07-04T02:29:33+00:00</updated><id>https://kuramu1108.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Po Craft</title><subtitle>The professional publishing platform</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Coffee Enthausiast’s Life @ Fukuoka, Japan</title><link href="https://kuramu1108.github.io/coffee-enthusiasts-life-at-fukuoka-japan" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Coffee Enthausiast’s Life @ Fukuoka, Japan" /><published>2021-07-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-07-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://kuramu1108.github.io/coffee-enthusiasts-life-at-fukuoka-japan</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kuramu1108.github.io/coffee-enthusiasts-life-at-fukuoka-japan">&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, this is Po from the Development centre&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am glad to be able to introduce how I enjoy my WFH life during pandemics.
Joined the company as a new grad last November, I had to start working from home right after that due to the pandemic.
I am strong caffeine-addicted, so losing access to free coffee in the office upset me quite a lot.
I started to brew my own coffee from bean to cup since 2017 while I was in Sydney, and I thought that now might be a good time to start my home coffee life in Japan.
I start to build up my little coffee corner in my small kitchen for the past 6 months and I am going to introduce 3 ways I brew coffee at home, ordered from easy to complicated methods.
Cold-brew
Pourover
Espressos&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cold-brew
First of all, cold brew is a way of brewing coffee where we just simply immerse coffee grounds in the water.
This is probably one of the simplest ways to brew coffee as all you need are a cold brewer and some coarse-grind coffee, fit it into a cold-brewer (which you could get one for 1500–3000 yen) and leave it in the fridge for 12–24 hours.
The coffee brew this way often has less acidity and more chocolate-ish flavour, which goes really well with milk 👌, also there are chilled so good for the incoming summertime
Pour-over
Secondly, pour-over, which is one of the most popular brewing methods around the world and also popular for home brewers. Also known as filter coffee or drip coffee.
To make a pour-over coffee, you would need a dripper, some paper filter, a cup/carafe, a pouring kettle, a coffee scale and maybe a hand grinder if you want to grind it yourself. (That’s a lot of gadgets lol)
Pour-over coffee often tastes cleaner and highlight the characteristics of the coffee beans you used
Espresso
Lastly, the big-name ESPRESSO. For this, you need an espresso machine and maybe a good grinder as well. Espresso is extracted with hot water and high pressure, so it is quite hard to brew one without a proper machine.
Since we used less water to brew, we could taste richer texture and flavour of the coffee
I bought an entry-level home-used espresso machine earlier this year, which is also capable of milk frothing as well, so I enjoy making latte art every day.
The upside of brewing your own coffee at home is you get to pick any coffee beans you want. There are many roasters and cafes out there in Fukuoka selling their own blends and single-origin coffee, most of them also grind coffee for you upon request.
My Recommended cafe to buy beans (online shop available):
https://www.manucoffee.com/
https://rec-coffee.com/en
https://connectcoffe.thebase.in/
If you are a coffee enthusiast like me, or just want to enjoy a cup of good coffee at home, I would recommend start trying to brew your own coffee and enjoy the learning process as well :)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Po-Hao Chen</name></author><category term="coffee" /><category term="fukuoka" /><summary type="html">Hi everyone, this is Po from the Development centre</summary></entry></feed>